Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- Hudson Basin Region--Conclusions and Recommendations (Volume I), 1975 (Box 30, Folder 77)
- Hudson Basin Region--Findings (Volume II), 1975 (Box 30, Folder 78)
- Hudson Valley Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 79)
- Human Affairs Program, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 80)
- College of Human Ecology, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 81)
- Human Nutrition Research--The Role of the Federal Government, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Correspondence--I, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Indirect Cost Rates, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Industrial and Labor Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Institute of Food Science and Marketing Advisory Council, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Center of International Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1975 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Isles of Shoals, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Correspondence--J, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Correspondence--K, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Correspondence--L, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Lake Champlain, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Law School, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Libraries, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Long Island Facilities, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Members of Assembly, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Members of Congress, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Governor's Office, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Senators, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Correspondence--M, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Management Confidential, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Management Systems and Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Maple Producers, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Miner Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Minority Faculty, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Monthly Indicators, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Mountain Pride, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Correspondence--Mc, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Correspondence--N, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Native Americans, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- New Faculty Reception, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- New York Farmers, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- New York State Banker's Association, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- New York State Fair, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- New York Soil Conservation, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- New York State Farm Electrification Council, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- New York State Flower Industries, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- New York State Grange, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- New York State Seed Association, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- New York State Soil Conservation Districts Association Inc., 1975 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- North Carolina, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Nutritional Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 49-51)
- Correspondence--O, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Cornell Institute of Occupational Education, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- Orange County Vegetable Growers, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- Organization of Tropical Studies, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 55)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 56)
- Correspondence--P, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- Payroll, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- Pesticides and Chemicals, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 60)
- Pesticides-Chemical Program, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 61)
- Physical Plant Operations, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 62)
- Physiology, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 63)
- Professor-at-Large, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 64)
- Publications, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 65)
- Purchasing, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 66)
- Correspondence--Q, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 67)
- Quadrangle Restoration Committee, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 68)
- Correspondence--R, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 69)
- Recycling, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 70)
- Regents and Advisory Committee Report--Financial Problems of Postsecondary Institutions, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 71)
- Office of Registrar, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 72)
- Agricultural Research, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 73)
- Retiring Faculty Recognition--University Faculty, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 74)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 75)
- ROTC, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 76)
- Rural Development--Chenango County, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 77)
- Rural Development--Clinton County, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 78-79)
- Rural Development Act (Title V), 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 80)
- Correspondence--S, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 81)
- Salaries, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 82)
- Salary Adjustments, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 83)
- Office of Scholarship and Financial Aid, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 84)
- Science, Technology, and Society Program (STS), 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 85)
- Sea Grant--Governing Board Meeting, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 86)
- Sea Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Sea Grant Program, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Sea Grant Proposal (Volume I), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Sea Grant Proposal (Volume II), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Sea Grant Newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Sea Grant Newspapers, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Scholarships, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- New York State Poultry Industry Coordinated Effort, Inc. (SPICE). (SPICE), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- State Appropriations for Agricultural Research, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Steward, F. C., 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Dean of Students, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Surplus Equipment, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Correspondence--T, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Teaching Assistants, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Tuition, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Correspondence--U, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Uihlein Farm, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- United Way, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Cornell University Press, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- University Senate, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Center of Urban Development Research, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- USDA, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- United States Plant, Soil and Nutrition Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Correspondence--V, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Vacant Faculty Positions, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Valatie, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Veterinary College, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Correspondence--W, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Water Resource and Marine Science Center, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Wayne County Migrant Program, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Wine Meeting, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Status of Women (Rose, Ann), 1976 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Correspondence--XYZ, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Ad Hoc Committee for Zimbabwe, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Biological Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Biological Sciences--Executive Committee, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Biological Sciences--Accessory Instructions, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Biological Sciences Newsletter, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Biochemistry (Gaylord, J. L.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Ecology (Levin, S. A.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Genetics (Stinson, H. T.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Neurobiology (Keeton, W. T.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Wiegand Herbarium (Clausen, R. T.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Assistant to the President (Barlow, J. R.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Assistant to the Provost (Jones, W. D.), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Assistant to the Provost for State Relations (Allee, D.), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Board of Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Counsel (Stamp, N. R.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Dean of the Faculty (Saunders, B. W.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- President (Corson, Dale R), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Provost (Knapp, D. C.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Senior Vice President Search, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 55)
- State Relations (Allee), 1976 (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Treasurer (Peterson, A. H), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 57)
- Vice President for Administration (Lawrence, S. A.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 58)
- Vice President for Campus Affairs (Gurowitz, D. W.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 59)
- Vice President for Public Affairs (Ramin, R. M.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 60)
- Vice President for Research (Cooke, W. D.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 61)
- Vice President (Barlow, Mark), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 62)
- Vice Provost (Fessenden-Raden, June), 1976 (Box 32, Folder 63)
- Vice Provost (McKeegan, Paul), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 64)
- Committee of Chairman, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 65)
- Deans' Council, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 66)
- Deans and Cornell University Executive Staff Meeting, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 67)
- Deans and Directors (D&D) Agendas, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 68)
- D&D Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 69-70)
- Department Heads' Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 71)
- Provost-Statutory Deans' Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 72)
- Statutory Deans' Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 73)
- SUNY--Annual Report for 1974-1975, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 74)
- SUNY--Assistant Chancellor for Special Projects (Neff, Charles B.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 75)
- SUNY--Associate Chancellor for Policy and Planning (Ingler, Charles W.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 76)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 77-80)
- SUNY--Budget Director (Anslow), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 81)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Boyer, Ernest L.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 82)
- SUNY--Chancellor's Report, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 83)
- SUNY--Deputy to the Chancellor, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 84)
- SUNY--Enrollment, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 85)
- SUNY--Executive Vice Chancellor (Kelly, James F.), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 86)
- SUNY--Faculty Grants for the Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 87)
- Faculty Senate, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
- SUNY--Monthly Report, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- SUNY--Newsletter and Releases, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- SUNY--Conference of Presidents, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
- SUNY--Provost for Graduate Education and Research (Murray, Daniel H.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs (Dearing, Bruce), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Campus Development (Lanford, Oscar E.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance and Business (Spindler, Harry K.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Personnel and Employee Relations (MacKenzie, Kenneth M.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations (Komisar, Jerome B.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for University Affairs (Thorne, Clifton), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Women, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical College, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical College Presidents' Meeting, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Utica-Rome, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Community Colleges, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Circular Letters (Kennedy, W. K.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
- Circular Letters (Spencer, J. W.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Associate Dean (Spencer, J. W.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Director Administrative Operations (Brown, Robert B.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Coordinator of Planning (Metz, J. F.), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Palm, Charles E. (Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor of Agricultural Sciences), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Agricultural Economics, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 28-30)
- Agricultural Economics--Bulletins, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 32-33)
- Agronomy, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Animal Science, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 35-57)
- Animal Science Headship, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Livestock Industry in Northern New York, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Animal Science--Beef Cattle, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Animal Science Farm, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Communication Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Media Services, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Communication Arts Presentation to the Deans and Directors, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Education, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 46-48)
- Education Proposal (Jenkins, Lehman, and Toomey), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Entomology, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Occupational Education, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 51)
- Cooperative Extension, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3-Jan)
- Ozbun, Jim L., 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- County Agents, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Cooperative Extension Association, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Cooperative Extension Program, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Finance and Business Office, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Floriculture, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Landscape Architecture, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Food Science, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Cooperative Extension Programs, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- 4-H, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Geneva, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 14-15)
- Long Island Ornamentals Research Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Microbiology, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Pesticide Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Institute of Food Science, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- International Agriculture Development (IAD), 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 20-22)
- Mann Library, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Natural Resources, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 24-26)
- Fish Management Report--Brandon Park, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Biothermal Laboratory, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Geological Survey Professional Paper 964, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Plant Breeding, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Biometrics Unit--Annual Report, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Plant Pathology, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Pomology, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Poultry Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Poultry Industry Advisory Council, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Research, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 36-37)
- Resident Instruction, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 38-39)
- Applicants, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Placement Summary, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Rural Sociology, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Vegetable Crops, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Processing Vegetable Conference, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Faculty Council of Representatives, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Graduate School, General Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- IAD Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Natural Resources Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 49-50)
- New York State Soil and Water Conservation Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- Publications Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- University Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
- Agriculture Faculty Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
- Agriculture Faculty Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Research, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 10-13)
- Research--Plant Genetics, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 14-15)
- Research--Photosynthesis, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 16-18)
- Research--Nitrogen Fixation, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Commission on Purposes and Priorities, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 20-22)
- SUNY--University Commission on Purposes and Priorities, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 23-24)
- SUNY--Statistical Data on Teaching Load and Instruction, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Research and Graduate Review, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 27-29)
- Course Level Analysis, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Reports of the University Commission on Purposes and Priorities, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Final Report of the University Commission on Purposes and Priorities, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- SUNY--Report on Part-Time Students, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
- OTA--Drafts and Final Report, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
- Biological Nitrogen Fixation (Wittwer, S. H.), 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- OTA, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
- OTA, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
- Kasetsart University, 1967-1974 (Box 36, Folder 14-15)
- "A Day in the Life of a Cow in Clover" (Johnstone-Wallace, D. B. and WKK), 1941 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Speeches--Agricultural Alumni Luncheon, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Speech--Agricultural Faculty Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Speech--Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Speech--Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Speech--Agricultural Research and Education--Decisions Affecting Their Future, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Speech--"Agriculture, Teaching, Research, and Extension", 1975 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Speech--Alumni Breakfast, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Speech--Animal Science, Telling the Story of Animal Science to Legislatures (Airy, John, Des Moines, Iowa), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Speech--Introduction Comments for Agricultural Leaders' Forums, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Speeches--"A Place to Stand" (Gould, Samuel B.), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Speech--"Benefits of Agricultural Research", 1975 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Speech--Welcome--Best Management Practices for Agriculture and Viticulture, Rochester, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Speech--Botany, Welcome to the Society for Economic Botany, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Speech--Boyer, Ernest "Public Hearing Board of Regents on the Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education", 1976 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Speech--Brady, Dr. N. C., 1973 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Speech--"Causes and Methods of Handling Student Unrest," Foundation for American Agriculture, Chicago, Illinois, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Center for Environmental Education, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- "Challenges Facing the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Science," New York State Horticultural Society, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Speech--"Changing World" (Dean of the University of Arizona), 1972 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Speech--"Chemistry and Genetics: The Foundation for Modern Agriculture," Rochester (Large), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Civil Disobedience (from the Journal of Philosophy), 1961 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Speeches--Community Colleges, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Comments on Cooperative Extension (CEC Meeting), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Cornell and the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Today, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Cornell Fund and Alumni Speeches, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Council of Agricultural Organization, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- "Damn the Torpedoes--Full Speed Ahead!" (Gould, Samuel B.), 1970 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Dyson, John S. "Wanted: A Public Enterprise System", 1976 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Speech--"Education and the Economic Advancement of Minority Groups in the United States" (Brimmer, Andrew F.), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Education, Production, Packaging, and Delivery, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Education--Production, Packaging and Delivery, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Effects of Budget Cuts on Programs of the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Geneva and Ithaca, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Efficiency of Agricultural Production in the Northeast, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Speech--Environment, Extension Program in Agriculture and the Environment, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 50)
- "Expanding Opportunities" (Gould), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Extension, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 52)
- Cornell Extension Club, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 53)
- Speech--Extension Conference, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Extension, Presidents of Extension Association, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Farm Prices-"Strike, Bargain or What"(Brunk, Max), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Food for Billions, American Society of Agronomy, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 57)
- Speeches--Miscellaneous (WKK), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 58)
- Foreign Aid and the Brain Drain (Perkins, James A.), 1966 (Box 36, Folder 59)
- The Future Role of Land-Grant Colleges in the Northeast, Northeast Agronomy Management, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 60)
- The Future of New York's Agriculture, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 61)
- Speech--Future Role of the Cornell College of Agriculture and Life Sciences in a Rapidly Changing Agriculture, Cornell Nutrition Conference, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 62)
- Speech--Fall Management SUNY Presidents, Saratoga Springs (Gould, Samuel), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 63)
- Grass-Roots Founders and Grass-Roots Prodders: The Source of Venture and Renewal for Democratic Education (Neufeld, Maurice), 1972 (Box 36, Folder 64)
- The Great American Dream: Education for Work? (Nyquist, Ewald), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 65)
- University of California at Berkeley Campus (Heyns, Rogers), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 66)
- Higher Education's Collapse--Empire State Report, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 67)
- Speech--Ho-Nun-De-Kah Barbecue, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 68)
- Speech--"How Are We to Support Our University Programs In Scientific Research and Education" (Long, F. A.), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 69)
- "How Much Support Should New York State Provide for Agricultural Research?", 1975 (Box 36, Folder 70)
- Implementing Pest Management Programs--"The Role of the Land-Grant Universities in Developing" (Palm, C. E.), 1972 (Box 36, Folder 71)
- Importance of Agricultural Research (WKK), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 72)
- Importance of Agriculture to the Urban Community, Rochester, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 73)
- Speeches--Importance of Teaching (WKK), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 74)
- Johnson, A. A. "New Demands on Public Service of the Land-Grant University-USDA System," Washington D.C., 1976 (Box 36, Folder 75)
- "Lessons of Our Land-Grant Past," Chicago (WKK), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 76)
- Livestock Industry Speech, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 77)
- Speech--Long Island Dedication, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 78)
- New York Agriculture Benefits the Economy of the Northeast, Ontario County Farm Bureau, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 79)
- Focus on New York's Agriculture-Roots of Empire, New York State Bankers Association, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 80)
- Parent's Reception, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 81)
- Speech--Penn Yan Alumni, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 82)
- Speeches at the Regents of the University of the State of New York (Rockefeller, Bowker, and Gould), 1970 (Box 36, Folder 83)
- Speech--"The Future of the Strategic Arms Race: Options for the 1970's" (Rathjens, George W.), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 84)
- Speeches--Remarks to Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 85)
- Trustees of SUNY, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 86)
- Speech Materials, 1968-1972 (Box 36, Folder 87)
- On Ideals and Experience (Perkins, James A.), 1967 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- "Manifestoes of Societal Change: An Agenda for Higher Education" (Leagans, J. Paul. Paul;), 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- New Demands on Public Service of the Land Grant University-USDA System (Johnson, A. A.), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Speeches-New York Bankers School, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- New York Dairy Herd Improvement Committee (NYDHI)--Meeting the Educational and Research Needs of Commercial Agriculture and Society (WKK), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- New York State Horticultural Society Speech, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Speech--"Organization and Administrative Structure of Agricultural Programs in the Land-Grant Universities" (Frolic, E. F.), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Partnership with SUNY--Extension Conference (WKK), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- "Paying the Bill for College" (Silber, John Boston University), 1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)